[theme music playing]
[laughs]
-[Natalie] Hello, Lover.
-[Jepoy] Where are my weapons?
If you want it, come and get it!
[laughs]
Mama, everything is ready.
The buyer wants to meet me personally.
So, why don't you just stay here
and hold the fort while I'm gone?
It's a wiretapping device.
That way, we can record
and listen in on Red Dragon's transaction.
[Lily] If something doesn't go as planned,
we'll be there right away.
[Helena] Emilia will
eventually lead our group,
so I want you to respect her.
[Diego] We can't afford to fail, Lily.
We have to catch Red Dragon in the act.
Police! Don't move!
[gunfire]
Let's move! What are you waiting for?
[Lily] Got you.
Anna? It's not what you think, Anna.
[Lily] I know we're in the middle
of a war, Diego.
But I think it's worth the fight
when you aren't alone.
From now on, let's make it official.
Will you be mine?
[Diego] I'm all yours.
The problem is, Mama,
you're left with nothing.
Your account is frozen.
Your properties and assets are gone.
That's where you're wrong, Emilia.
[Diego] So, if Red Dragon is hiding money,
I know where we can find it.
[Arnaldo] Diego only manages
to score now because
I'm watching from the sidelines.
Now that I'm back,
I'll put him in his rightful place.
My baby brother.
Arnaldo.
Ah… Diego.
You seem to be coming here more often.
Sorry about that, Lily.
But I heard about what happened to Diego.
I just want to make sure he's okay.
So, are you okay, Diego?
Were you hurt?
Thanks, Arnaldo. But, Lily and I are fine.
Besides, what matters
is that Red Dragon's finally behind bars.
That's good to hear.
I know what my grandmother did was wrong.
And, I know my family's done
a lot of horrible things.
I do feel guilty for all that too.
But I guess all I can do now
is pray for them,
and hope that truth and justice prevail
in the end.
I also hope you two stay safe
while fighting
for what's right.
[tense music plays]
Your hand's bleeding.
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Just a scratch.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah. I'll be fine.
[Arnaldo exhales]
Well, thank you for visiting your brother.
But, we have to go
because we have important errands to run.
-Let's go.
-Wait, Lily.
Uh…
Sorry, I promise this will be quick.
I just wanted to thank you.
For taking care of my brother.
Take care.
Thanks, Arnaldo.
Let's go.
[unsettling music playing]
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
-Take care.
-We'll be going.
-All right.
-Get that treated, okay?
Yes, will do.
-Thank you.
-This is nothing.
[unsettling music playing]
[clicks tongue]
Here, Anna. Drink something.
[sniffles, exhales]
I really can't believe
Jepoy did that to you.
Just say the word,
and I'll go teach him a lesson.
Forget it, Marlon.
That'll just make things worse.
Sorry.
I'm just really mad at him right now.
He really shouldn't have done that to you.
[sobbing]
[soft music playing]
It's okay. Just let it all out.
[rattling]
[Jepoy] Natalie!
Open the door!
Open the damn door!
[panting]
Can you calm down, Madrigal?
You're like a raging bull!
[squeals]
Are you ready for round two? Huh?
Anna and I already broke up.
Are you happy now?!
Was this what you wanted?!
Your romance with that woman
was doomed from the start!
And, in case you've forgotten…
you were mine first.
She just took you away from me.
Or did you forget?
You belong to me.
Do you understand?
I trusted Jepoy.
How could he do this to me?
Where did I go wrong, Marlon?
Is it because I couldn't give
what Natalie was ready to?
Isn't my love enough for him?
Well, I guess it's my fault too.
I fooled myself into thinking
he actually loved me,
but he didn't.
Turns out he'd much rather
take care of himself.
Then again…
I guess men are just that selfish.
Don't say that.
Not all men are like Jepoy.
[squeals]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[both breathing heavily]
-[grunts]
-[shrieks]
[dramatic music playing]
Jepoy's an idiot.
I can't believe he cheated
on a woman like you.
You know, Anna…
one day, you'll find a man
who'll treat you right.
The kind who'll never lie, hurt,
or leave you.
Who knows…
he might just be hanging around.
You'll find him, eventually.
One day, I'm sure he'll have
the guts to tell you…
just how he feels.
And then, I'm sure
he'll be ready to make you feel
what true love is like.
The kind of love that you deserve.
[piano music playing]
I've got to go.
[tense music playing]
We'll pretend to buy some drinks.
Ma'am?
How much for the juice?
Do you want some juice?
Sure. What else do they have?
All right. We'll have two, please.
[Diego whispers] What?
Just wait. I'll go first.
Okay.
Here you go.
Looks like it'll be hard to get in.
This place is heavily guarded.
We'll need help from the cops.
No.
Not yet, Diego.
For now, I don't want anyone else
to know about this.
First, we have to make sure
that Red Dragon's money
really is in there.
Don't forget, she has way
too many connections.
I don't want her ruining any of our plans.
[upbeat music playing]
Boys, go in. Break time.
Wait, don't start the car.
[tense music playing]
[chuckling]
You should have seen their faces.
They believed the good Arnaldo act.
I don't know why.
Well, I would dare say
that it's really good, my son.
You know…
just continue spying on Lily and Diego.
Because we should always be one step ahead
of all their plans.
Noted, Grandpa. I'll do that.
Well, speaking of,
when I got there,
they were in a hurry to leave.
They said they needed
to be somewhere important.
Voices inside my head keep telling me…
it has something to do with Grandma.
They're going to do something
to keep Grandma in prison.
Well, just like what I told you.
We need to know
what those two are planning.
We need to weaken them from the inside.
And with you…
[chuckling] the good Arnaldo being there…
they will never know what hit them.
Well…
to the fall of Lily and Diego
and the rise of the Ardientes.
I'll drink to that.
[glasses clink]
[tense music playing]
Twenty minutes.
They have a twenty-minute break.
That's the amount of time
we have to scale the wall.
Let's go.
[car engine starts]
Give this to Magbanua.
He knows what to do with that.
Emilia!
Oh, please join me!
What's happening to your mother?
It seems like she doesn't
want to leave prison.
Does she like it in there?
Ask her when
the housewarming party will be
so that we can visit her.
Go ahead, Papa. Laugh all you want.
But you know, this is all temporary, Papa.
When we both get back on our feet,
we'll forget you even exist.
[laughs]
You'll forget I exist?
Hey!
Even if you and your mother join forces,
where would you get power from?
Your mother has fallen far from grace.
All the riches of the much-ballyhooed
Red Dragon are gone.
That's what you think, Papa.
It ain't over until the fat lady sings.
Or should I say the Red Dragon sings.
Emilia, how can she make
a comeback when she's dirt poor?
The authorities seized all her assets.
She has no money left.
Didn't you learn anything from me?
Money makes the world go around.
And I have it in all kinds of currency.
Wow. Clearly, Papa,
you underestimated Mama.
What the police have
is only the tip of the iceberg.
You know, Red Dragon
is more than what meets the eye.
And one more thing, Papa.
You know, I will inherit
everything Red Dragon owns.
All the things that you see and don't.
[laughs]
Who's laughing now, Papa?
[tense music playing]
No matter how solid a wall is built,
cracks form eventually.
And that's what I saw earlier.
But Lily, our biggest problem
is the guards.
There are way too many of them.
Every corner of that place
is heavily guarded.
We can't get past them.
I know, Diego.
Those CCTV cameras
and those walls never rest.
But since those guards are only human,
they get tired too.
Boys, go in. Break time.
We just need to wait.
Let's wait for an opening.
Our mission doesn't have
any room for errors.
[tense music building up]
It looks like your grandma's
keeping a secret.
Sneaky, sneaky, Red Dragon.
But never mind.
I know how she operates.
A crime lord of her caliber
will not allow something like this.
She will not allow her entire fortune
to disappear just like that.
So, are you saying that Grandma
still has some money hidden?
You are absolutely correct.
Of course, we need to get
our share of her fortune.
We're family, right?
And an Ardiente will always find a way
to get what he wants.
[laughs]
[piano music playing]
Sorry. Sorry. Did I scare you?
How are Lily and Diego?
Do you have an update?
I don't.
Camia, I want to help them.
Sure, Damian.
[tense music playing]
Come on. Let's take a quick break.
This is it. This is the blind spot.
We only have a few minutes
before the roving guards come back.
Come on.
[door opens]
[pensive music playing]
Are you lost, Julio Ardiente?
No.
I am exactly where I would like to be.
Visiting me in jail?
For what? To laugh at me?
My darling, Helena.
I'm not here to laugh at you.
Nor will I try to be a comedian
to make you laugh.
But
you might laugh
when you hear what I'm about to tell you.
[tense music playing]
And you might not be able
to contain your excitement
once you hear my offer.
An alliance is formed between two factions
to defeat a common enemy.
Of course, I know you know that.
You and I have a common enemy.
Lily Cruz.
And I also know that you know
two dragons are better than one.
Are you listening to me so far?
I'm listening.
Okay.
What if I can tell you
that I can offer you
that alliance against Lily Cruz,
and, most importantly,
that I can guarantee your freedom?
[tense music playing]
A stare.
Is that all I'm going to get from you?
No feisty reaction?
No passionate declaration?
What do you want me to say?!
A big, fat, juicy yes
would be a good start!
You're too impatient!
I am not easy and that
is what you liked about me!
I am not courting you. So don't test me!
This is a business offer.
If you really know how to strategize,
and if you're as intelligent
as I think you are,
you will not dare refuse my offer!
You haven't learned your lesson!
You should never raise
your voice at a dragon
if you don't want to be eaten alive.
[tense music playing]
The inside is teeming with guards.
And the money pit is pretty far from here.
I need to see what's inside, Diego.
I have to.
So we can make
all the necessary preparations.
Be careful, okay?
What? He said that?
Yes.
And what did you say?
I reacted like a true-blue dragon should.
[exhales] Good.
Because you shouldn't fall
for Papa's trap, you know.
I have a feeling he needs
something from you,
that's why he's acting like that.
Wait.
What if he already knows
about your hidden wealth?
You know, Emilia,
I was wondering that too.
Aside from Romulo,
who's now rotting in prison,
you, baby girl,
are the only person who knows
about my hidden wealth.
You didn't mention that
to your father, did you?
Emilia, how can she make a comeback
when she's dirt poor?
The authorities seized all her assets.
Clearly, Papa, you underestimated Mama.
What the police have
is only the tip of the iceberg.
What?!
Hell no, Mama!
I would never say that to Papa!
I know how confidential that is.
Me, tell him about your hidden wealth?
No! I didn't tell him.
I swear my life on it.
Never mind.
He'll have a hard time
stealing it, anyway.
Because it is being guarded
by the fiercest dragon of them all.
Yes, a dragon.
A big, imposing monster.
You think you can beat it?
Outsmart it?
But nothing can escape
its all-seeing eyes.
Galang, Galang.
Could you check the left wing?
[Red Dragon] Because the dragon's eyes
can see everything, every
day, twenty-four-seven.
It guards my billions' worth
of cash and treasury bonds.
And whoever dares provoke the dragon…
will spontaneously combust.
[evil laughter]
[awkward laughter]
Boss, the area is clear.
I'm going back to my post.
Okay.
Okay, boys.
Break time's over. Back to your posts now.
[tense music playing]
Let's go.
I'll leave that to you.
[upbeat music playing]
It won't be easy to get
to Helena's hidden wealth.
We have to use force. We need manpower.
Leave it to me.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello, Atty. Fisher?
What?
Come on, let's go home.
Bless you.
Grandma declined your offer?
[scoffs]
Yes.
Because your grandma
is silly, selfish, stubborn…
And stupid.
Sorry, I had to finish your sentence.
But, seriously.
You're offering her a lifeline,
and then she refuses.
Maybe she figured out
we're after her money?
But, what's stopping us from stealing it?
Well, you know…
whether or not
your grandma accepts my offer
to form an alliance, it doesn't matter
because I already have the power.
Her money is just going
to be icing on the cake.
Uh…
Okay. Wait, I'm confused.
Earlier, you wanted to steal
from her, and now, you don't.
So, which is it?
Why the sudden change of heart?
You know, grandson, sometimes,
you just have to wait,
and let situations take
their natural course.
Anyway…
whatever happens,
I have my eyes on the prize.
And I assure you that
those riches will go to us.
Just us, and not your mom.
Because if not,
I'm going to make sure
that no one else gets it.
I'm going to burn all that money into ash.
Don't worry.
Okay. Now, let's eat.
Okay.
Bring those here. Thank you.
[clears throat] Emilia?
Is it true that your mother's
got tons of cash hidden?
And where did you hear that from?
I just know. It's true, isn't it?
Um, I'm sorry to disappoint you,
my dear husband, but, my lips are sealed.
I cannot reveal anything about my mom
because I made a promise to her.
Come on, everyone in the family
knows each other's secrets.
And, so does the town.
You're not hiding anything anymore, right?
And what do you mean by that?
That your father wants to help
free your mother, doesn't he?
I doubt it, Raul.
My mother would never ask
for help from Papa.
She'd rather be in jail
than accept anything from him.
Oh, really?
So, who helped your mother
get out of jail?
What are you talking about?
[chuckles]
[tense music playing]
Only ten minutes ago,
the authorities made the decision
to dismiss the charges
against Helena Montoya,
who is suspected
to be the syndicate leader,
Red Dragon.
According to the reports,
there is insufficient evidence
to prove that Helena Montoya
is Red Dragon.
[chuckles]
Why do I get the feeling
you had something to do with this?
[chuckles]
[reporter] The entrapment operation
that led to Ms. Montoya's arrest
was said to be a frame-up
set up by her business competitors.
Stay tuned to Ardiente News. This is--
[Marlon] Anna!
Anna!
Good thing I caught you.
I was just at the center.
Yeah, I just stopped by to see
my sick student. What's wrong?
Red Dragon's case was dismissed.
What?
But, Lily and Auntie Camia…
-Let's go see them.
-Yeah.
-How dare you!
-Camia.
You shameless liar! You're a liar!
You are Red Dragon!
There's no way you can hide!
-Camia, calm down.
-You don't understand, Damian.
They always just manage
to escape from the law!
-I know.
-They're nothing but liars!
I know.
I understand how you feel.
Tell me, Attorney,
that this is not happening.
You said we filed
a strong case against her.
-Yes, it's true.
-So, what happened?
We even had fiscal evidence!
You know how business in Ardiente works.
And, my gut tells me Red Dragon paid--
[Lily] Enough.
What I want to know is,
do we still have a chance?
The case hasn't gone
through a hearing yet.
So, we can file it again
and it won't be double jeopardy.
Okay. I'll file it again.
Go see Myla right now.
I'm already here, Lily.
Myla?
[suspenseful music playing]
LILY, THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
BUT I'M SORRY. I CAN'T DO IT. MYLA.
[groans]
Lily!
Even Myla is gone.
She was the only one left
who could testify for us
and now she's gone.
How can I file the case again,
if I don't have anyone
who can testify for me?
You do.
I'll testify against Red Dragon.
-Diego.
-Lily.
Their efforts to prove that
I am Red Dragon have failed.
Because the truth finally prevailed
over their baseless accusations.
Today, justice is served.
I am not Red Dragon.
And no one can prove
I am that wicked crime leader.
I am Helena Montoya.
I am a private citizen.
A concerned citizen,
who wants to do nothing
but serve and love the town of Ardiente.
Onward, Ardiente!
[applause]
Go ahead. Smile and celebrate.
Because once I'm done with you,
you'll never be able to smile again.
[tense music playing]
Congratulations.
Red roses for you, Red Dragon.
You think it's going to be that easy?
You think I'll let you
off the hook so easily?
Mark my words. I won't stop.
Even if I have to file
multiple cases against you,
I'll do it just to prove that you,
Helena Montoya, are Red Dragon.
Go ahead. Who's going to believe you?
[chuckles]
You don't have a witness.
The Big Four are dead.
And so is Mercedes.
And your witness just backed out.
[laughs]
Who's going to prove that I am Red Dragon?
I will.
I'll testify against you.
Really?
You?
You'll testify against me, Diego Torillo?
Well, it's your word against mine.
You might be forgetting
that you were my ally once.
And I'll make it appear
you're testifying against me
because the real leader
of this organization
is none other than, Lily.
Then while the citizens
of Ardiente are crucifying you,
I am going to leave this
detention area free as a bird.
Enough time for me to build
a new syndicate group.
What should I call my new syndicate?
Let's see.
Poison Ivy?
Oh! How about…
Tiger Lily?
I'll do that and make it appear
that you're the leader of that syndicate!
-You will, huh?!
-Stop hurting me! Ouch!
Help me! I'm being hurt!
Stop hurting me!
Oh my God! Did you see that?!
She's hurting me! Did you see that?!
People like Lily Cruz are the reason
why I'm involved in this case!
It's her!
Please, officer! Arrest her!
[camera shutter clicking]
Please, arrest her!
Officer, arrest her! She was hurting me!
You're such a good actress!
But the real criminal here is you!
Just wait because I'll prove
you're a crime lord.
I am telling you, I'm going to prove it!
Please, arrest her!
-Come with me outside, ma'am.
-Don't touch me!
Did you see that?
I was just here, you know.
I didn't even have bodyguards.
I feel so helpless and she just
attacked me with that guy,
Diego Torillo. I feel so violated!
After I've been proven innocent,
she's going to do that to me?
Why? Why would she do that?
I can't even think of a reason.
She used to be my friend, you know.
-Lily.
[door slams shut]
Lily!
-[knocking on door]
-Lily!
Lily, open the door!
-[knocking on door]
-Lily!
[Diego] Lily!
-[knocking on door]
-Lily!
[knocking on door]
[Diego] Lily!
-[glass shatters]
-[screams]
All of my efforts, wasted!
[panting]
-Lily!
-Villanueva?
-Yes, ma'am?
-Get the keys from the study room.
-Hurry.
-Yes, ma'am.
Lily!
[dramatic music playing]
Everything I did was for nothing.
[sniffles, sobs]
Now isn't the time to give up.
Keep fighting.
[Lily] I'll take justice
into my own hands.
If it's a fight that they want,
then I'll give it to them.
-What's going on, Papa?
-It's showtime. Viva Ardiente!
[henchman 1] What's your
plan now, Boss Jaguar?
The Ardientes have become more powerful
with Red Dragon on their side.
[henchman 2] Shouldn't we be
joining their group now?
Don't worry. We'll bring them down.
We couldn't get the court
to release a search warrant.
Wasn't the evidence we presented enough?
I am not a vigilante.
It's my job to make sure
the law is enforced.
The law of Lily Cruz will prevail.
[theme music playing]